[
  {
    "question": "the travel agency",
    "answer": "die Reiseagentur"
  },
  {
    "question": "the agency",
    "answer": "die Agentur"
  },
  {
    "question": "the city center",
    "answer": "das Stadtzentrum"
  },
  {
    "question": "the trip",
    "answer": "die Reise"
  },
  {
    "question": "the day",
    "answer": "der Tag"
  },
  {
    "question": "the meeting",
    "answer": "das Meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "the office",
    "answer": "das Büro"
  },
  {
    "question": "the customer",
    "answer": "der Kunde"
  },
  {
    "question": "the colleague",
    "answer": "der Kollege"
  },
  {
    "question": "the tourist",
    "answer": "der Tourist"
  },
  {
    "question": "the travel costs",
    "answer": "die Reisekosten"
  },
  {
    "question": "the reservation",
    "answer": "die Reservierung"
  },
  {
    "question": "the hotel",
    "answer": "das Hotel"
  },
  {
    "question": "the work",
    "answer": "die Arbeit"
  },
  {
    "question": "the morning",
    "answer": "der Morgen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the bicycle",
    "answer": "das Fahrrad"
  },
  {
    "question": "the car",
    "answer": "das Auto"
  },
  {
    "question": "the minute",
    "answer": "die Minute"
  },
  {
    "question": "the foot",
    "answer": "der Fuß"
  },
  {
    "question": "the train",
    "answer": "der Zug"
  },
  {
    "question": "the evening",
    "answer": "der Abend"
  },
  {
    "question": "the dog",
    "answer": "der Hund"
  },
  {
    "question": "the friend",
    "answer": "der Freund"
  },
  {
    "question": "the Friday",
    "answer": "der Freitag"
  },
  {
    "question": "the restaurant",
    "answer": "das Restaurant"
  },
  {
    "question": "the house",
    "answer": "das Haus"
  },
  {
    "question": "the child",
    "answer": "das Kind"
  },
  {
    "question": "the man/husband",
    "answer": "der Mann"
  },
  {
    "question": "the kebab",
    "answer": "der Kebab"
  },
  {
    "question": "the park",
    "answer": "der Park"
  },
  {
    "question": "to work",
    "answer": "arbeiten"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be located",
    "answer": "liegen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to plan",
    "answer": "planen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to sell",
    "answer": "verkaufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to begin",
    "answer": "beginnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to call",
    "answer": "telefonieren"
  },
  {
    "question": "to come",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be called",
    "answer": "heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to do/make",
    "answer": "machen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to drive",
    "answer": "fahren"
  },
  {
    "question": "to live",
    "answer": "wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to need",
    "answer": "brauchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to go/walk",
    "answer": "gehen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to play",
    "answer": "spielen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to eat",
    "answer": "essen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to cook",
    "answer": "kochen"
  }
]
